Guide to the Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records, 1978-1993 AIS.1993.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records
1978-1993
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Tri-State Conference on Steel
Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing
AIS.1993.10
85 Linear Feet (67 boxes and 30 oversized items)
The Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing was founded in 1979 as the Tri-State Conference on Steel, which was a coalition of labor unions and activists that fought the effects of deindustrialization. The group created or became involved in several regional projects concerning unemployment and plant closures, such as the Steel Valley Authority. This collection includes correspondence, newsletters, and meeting minutes regarding the activities of the Tri-State Council on Steel and Manufacturing.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing, Board of Directors, on August 3, 1993 and December 13, 1994.
History
The Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing was founded in 1979 as the Tri-State Conference on Steel, which was a coalition of labor unions and activists that fought the effects of deindustrialization. The organization created the Steel Valley Authority, which sought to publicly own closed mills through the use of eminent domain, as a means of keeping mills open and thousands of steelworkers on the job. Members were also involved in several regional projects concerning unemployment and plant closures. Tri-State also played an integral role in the grassroots movement to save Dorothy Six, a blast furnace at the US Steel Duquesne Works. The group supported bringing a MAGLEV train to Pittsburgh as a means of solving transportation and employment problems in the area.
Previous Citation
Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records, 1982-1993, AIS.1993.10, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
This collection includes correspondence, newsletters, and meeting minutes regarding the activities of the Tri-State Council on Steel and Manufacturing. Newspaper and magazine clippings concerning plant closures and the steel industry comprise a large portion of the collection. Also included are financial and fundraising records, as well as research material and reports.
Separated Material
Oversized materials can be found in cabinet drawers 5-4 and 5-5.
Related Material
Denominational Ministry Strategy Collection, 1973-1995, AIS.1989.07, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Robert Jurich Scrapbooks, 1981-1990, AIS.1990.15, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Rainbow Kitchen Records, 1974-1992, AIS.1991.10, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Mon Valley Unemployed Committee Records, 1980-1995, AIS.2002.02, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Manufacturing industries -- West Virginia; Manufacturing industries -- Ohio; Labor; Manufacturing industries -- Pennsylvania; Steel industry and trade -- Ohio; Steel industry and trade -- West Virginia; Steel industry and trade -- Pennsylvania; Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing; Tri-State Conference on Steel
- Staff Report, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Steel Valley Authority (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Wage Abuse in the Fast Food Industry, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Steel Retention Study, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Steel Valley Authority, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Steel Valley Authority Board of Directors, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Working Group Economic Development Committee (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Tri-State Monthly Meetings, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Tri-State Steering/Planning Committee, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Tri-State Strategic Planning (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Tri-State Steering Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Steel Valley Authority Funding (Box 1, Folder 13)
- USX Homestead Works Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Steel Valley Authority Proposals, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Steel Valley Authority, Competing Schemes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Steel Valley Authority, Carrie Furnace, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Borough Information (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Steel Valley Authority, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Affirmative Action (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Annual Awards Dinner, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Tri-State Annual Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Board and Committee Members (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Tri-State Board Meetings, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5-9)
- Bost Building Restoration, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Booster Clubs, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Brake and Switch (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Braun Baking, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Tri-State Budget, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Building Organizations Workshop, October 5-6, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Campaign For Human Development (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Carrie Furnaces (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Certificate of Registration for Charitable Solicitation (Box 2, Folder 18)
- City Pride Meeting, January 6, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Joe Magarac Dinner Mailing Lists (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Dislocated Workers Skill Survey (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Duquesne, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Documents, Proposals, Reports and Board Members (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Eastern Industrial Valleys Community of Faith, 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Electric Furnace (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plan, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Executive Committee, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Finance Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
- Finance Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
- Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Fundraising, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
- Homestead, 1987, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- House Bill 400 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- House Bill 63 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Lists of Group Members (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Membership/Committee 2, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Membership Meetings (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Mission Statement Development Plan (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Mon Valley Network, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- NABISCO, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- National Policy (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Tri-State Conference Call Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
- Office Equipment, Phones and Faxes (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
- Personnel Committee, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Personnel, Jim Benn (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Personnel, Lois Hill (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Personnel, Rose Schnitgen (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Personnel, Job Applicants (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Pittsburgh Economic Recovery, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Post Office Information (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Presidential Debate, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Proposals, Allegheny County Fund for Social Change, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Proposal, United Steelworkers of America, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Regional Industry Center, Cleveland, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Committee (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Southbank Industry Association, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Staff Reports and Schedules, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
- Staff Meetings, Agenda and Reports (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Progress Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Steel Valley Authority Memoranda (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Steel Valley Authority Newsletter, July 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Steel Valley Authority, Residents Committee (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Steel Valley Authority, A View From the Valley (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Tri-State Board Meetings, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Budget and Finance Information, 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Tri-State Calendar of Events, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Tri-State, Committee 2, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Contract between Tri-State and United Steelworkers of America (Box 4, Folder 10)
- CCAC Board Development (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Correspondence regarding Educational Materials (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Tri-State Finance Planning Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Legal Information (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Membership Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Documents (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Progress Report, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Reference, Articles on Tri-State (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Tri-State Slide Show (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Tri-State Staff Reorganization (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Tri-State Targeted Organizations and Pittsburgh Unions (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Weekly Reports, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Work Program, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Unemployed Groups and Actions Around the Country (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Mon Valley Unemployed Committee Rally, October 6, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Mon Valley Unemployed Committee Proposals (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Proposal for Labor Action on Unemployment (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Unemployment Benefits Legislation (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Mon Valley Unemployed Committee (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Mon Valley Unemployed Committee Newsletters (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Steelworker Rally, May 12, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Duquesne Layoffs Committee and Joint Local Actions (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Unemployment Organization Histories (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Unemployment International (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Unemployment Statistics (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Stress and Unemployment (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Women of Steel, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Steel People: Survival and Resilience in Pittsburgh's Mon Valley, 1986 (Box 5, Item 1)
- The Industrial North: The Future of Jobs, Producivity and Community, the IUP Conference on Industry and Society, October 21-23, 1982 (Box 5, Item 2)
- State of the Region: Western Pennsylvania, Ohio, and West Virginia a Sub-Region of Appalachia Study Paper and Proposal, 1983 (Box 5, Item 3)
- The Tri-State Program for Revitalizing and Resurecting the Pittsburgh Steel Industry by Bob Erickson, 1983 (Box 5, Item 4)
- Confronting the Crisis: The Challenge for Labor, Report to United Steelworkers of America, 1985 (Box 5, Item 5)
- Forging Revival and Renaissance: An Action Program for the Revitalization of the Mon Valley by James O. Pickard and the Pennsylvania Department of Commerce, 1986 (Box 5, Item 6)
- Reindustrialization from Below by Staughton Lynd (Box 5, Item 7)
- Forging Revival and Renaissance: Action Program for the Revitalization of the Mon Valley, Technical Supplement (Box 5, Item 8)
- State of the Region, Basic Steel, 1986 (Box 5, Item 9)
- Building on the Basics: The Final Report of the Mayor's Task Force on Steel and Southeast Chicago (Box 5, Item 10)
- Aliquippa Update: A Pittsburgh Milltown Struggles to Come Back, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Item 11)
- Trouble in Electric Valley: Local Leaders Assess the Difficult Future of Their Community, 1986 (Box 5, Item 12)
- Local Initiatives Support Cooperation, A Two Year Report, September 1, 1984 (Box 5, Item 13)
- Human Services Choices for Pennsylvanians, Interim Summary, 1985 (Box 5, Item 14)
- Regional Transportation Plan by Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, 1984 (Box 5, Item 15)
- Feasibility Study of the Duquesne Works Blast and Basic Oxygen Furnaces for United Steelworkers of America, Preliminary Report, January 28, 1985 (Box 5, Item 16)
- Against the Current 2, March-April 1986 (Box 5, Item 17)
- Study on the Demand and Supply of Semifinished Steel Products in the United States, Final Report, April 30, 1985 (Box 5, Item 18)
- Business Retention Study by PACE of Pittsburgh Consulting Group, March 10, 1986 (Box 5, Item 19)
- Point of View and The Ecumenical Great Lakes/Appalachian Project on the Economic Crisis, 1977-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Reactions of Other Regions to Deindustrialization (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Cleveland Rainbow Coalition, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- National Rainbow Coalition, Plant Closings Proposal, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- National Rainbow Coalition Convention, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- National Rainbow Coalition, Labor, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- National Rainbow Coalition, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Jesse Jackson Presidential Campaign, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Cleveland Rainbow Coalition Endorsement Issue, March 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- USWA Contacts, Local Unions in Districts 15 and 20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Denominational Ministry Strategy, Network to Save Mon-Ohio Valleys, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Right to Ratify (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Outreach, Network, 1st Labor Notes Workshop, National Unemployed Network Conference (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Comeback Conference, May 4-5, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
- National Rainbow Coalition First Biennial Convention, October 9-11, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- A View from the Mon Valley by Bob Erickson, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Directory of National Unions and Employee Associations, Supplement, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Solidarity Unionism by Staughton Lynd (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Down on the Farm, A Hays Daily News Special Report, June 21, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Mandating Social Prudence: A Handbook for Pension Investment, 1982 (Box 5, Item 20)
- Changing Work, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Item 21)
- Mail Appeal (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Legal Intern (Box 5, Folder 23)
- South Side Furnace, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, West Virginia (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Mountaineers for Sane Taxation (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Update, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Research Project, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Wheeling, WV, Jim Benn (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Tri-State Regional Reindustrialization Project, Contact Lists (Box 5, Folder 30)
- West Virginia Economic Summary, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Cleveland, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- West Virginia Economic Summary, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, Charleston, WV (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Sign-In Books, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Item 1-2)
- Labor Research Association 8th Annual Banquet Luncheon, November 20, 1983 (Box 6, Item 3)
- Beyond the Myths: The Families Helped By the AFDC Program by the Center on Social Welfare Policy and Law, 1985 (Box 6, Item 4)
- Worker-Writer Appointment Calendar: Reflections on Working and Living, Featuring Excerpts from the Mill Hunk Herald, 1986 (Box 6, Item 5)
- Checklist for Management of Firm Facing Mass Layoff or Closedown (Box 6, Item 6)
- Transcript of 'Organization of Production and Shop Floor Democracy' Chaired by Charles McCollester, October 29, 1983 (Box 6, Item 7)
- From the Mon Valley... The Steel Valley Authority is Formed... The Struggle Continues (Box 6, Item 8)
- House Subcommittee Report on Labor Law Cites Growing Politicization of NLRB, 1984 (Box 6, Item 9)
- National Unemployed Network: Graphics for Jobs and Justice (Box 6, Item 10)
- Presidential Election Results, Mickey Jarvis USWA, 1984 (Box 6, Item 11)
- Power of New Bedford, Massachusetts, to Acquire the Morse Cutting Tools Plant Through Eminent Domain, May 18, 1984 (Box 6, Item 12)
- A Magazine on Workplace Democracy Report on the Initial Workshop, October 31, 1981 (Box 6, Item 13)
- Armco Steel, Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- J&L Structural Inc., Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Cytemp, Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wean Industries Inc. Dongbu Steel Co., Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- LTV-Sumitomo Metals Industries Ltd., Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- PATrain, Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Steel Demand, Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Steel Research, Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Research, Pitt's Basic Metal Processing Research Institute, Clippings, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Steel, Connected Industries, Refractories, Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Steel, Connecting Industries, Shipping, Clippings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Steel-making Process and Technologies, Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Sharon Steel, Clippings, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- USX Steel Facilities, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal (Box 6, Folder 18-37)
- Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal (Box 7)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, USX National Works (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel Corp., Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania Steel Companies and Facilities, Clippings, 1985, 1988, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- West Virginia Steel Companies, Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Weirton, WV Steel Facilities, Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project: Natural Resources, Steel, 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel, Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Babcock and Wilcox Steel, Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Bethlehem Steel, Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Cyclops Steel, Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project: Natural Resources, Coal, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Steel, Connecting Industries, Coal, Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project: Natural Resources, Infrastructure, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project: Natural Resources, Great Lakes Inland Waterway (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Mon Valley Expressway, Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Steel, Connected Industries, Rail, Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Pennsylvania Toll Roads Feasibility Study Summary Report, June 1983 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Constructor, 1,979 Water Projects Backlogged by the Associated General Contractors of America, January 1985 (Box 8, Item 1)
- Infrastructure- The Aftermath and the Realization: A Call for Action by the Associated General Contractors of America (Box 8, Item 2)
- America's Infrastructure: Effects of Construction Spending by the Associated General Contractors of America (Box 8, Item 3)
- America's Infrastructure: A Plan to Rebuild By the Associated General Contractors of America, May 1983 (Box 8, Item 4)
- Pennsylvania Infrastructure Investment Authority (Pennvest), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Annual Report on Southwestern Pennsylvania's Bridge Conditions, February 1985 (Box 8, Item 5)
- Regional Transportation Plan by the Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, 1984 (Box 8, Item 6)
- Assessment of Proposed Lock Operation Curtailment on the Allegheny and Monongahela Rivers, 1982 (Box 8, Item 7)
- Tri-State Finances, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Tri-State Bills, 1981, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 20-23)
- Tri-State Petty Cash, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 24-26)
- Tri-State Bank Statements, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Tri-State Finance Reports, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Information regarding Boroughs in Western Pennsylvania (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
- Clippings Master File (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and Contacts, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Tri-State Meeting Agenda, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Tri-State Conference Membership Mailings, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Information (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Clippings, December 1984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Newsletters, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Newspaper Clippings, January 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Clippings: Steel Valley Authority and Save Dorothy Six Campaign, March 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Newspaper Clippings: Save Duquesne Campaign, February 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings, April-December 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4-7)
- Advertising Materials (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Caravan (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
- Canvassing Information (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Community Reinvestment Act, Banks (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Conference Notes and Transcripts, Regional Reindustrialization Project, December 7, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Duquesne Works/Dorothy Feasibility Study, Various Companies, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
- Economic Notes (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Ecumenical Task Force, Tri-State Coalition, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- General Motors, Saturn Campaign, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Industrial Parks, US Steel Information (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Pamphlet Layout (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Locker/Abrecht Associations, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Jobs with Peace/Freeze, Pennsylvania Conversion Conference Information (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Maps (Box 11, Folder 12)
- "Milltowns in the Pittsburgh Region", Carnegie Mellon University Feasibility Study, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Phelps Dodge Campaign, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Pollock, Richards and Associates (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Small Business Administration, Small Business/Cooperative Incubators, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Steel Processing Research Institute, University of Pittsburgh (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Steel Magazines (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Steel Technology Symposium, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 20-22)
- Wrestling Event (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Testimonies from Tri-state Members, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Tri-State/USWA Association (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Tri-State Newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 26-27)
- Minutes, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Pittsburgh City Council Activities, Personnel, and Information, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Gary Hart (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Senator John Heinz (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Minutes, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- McCreary Tire, Indiana County, PA (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Tri-State Conference Board Information, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Mesta, Tri-State (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Politicians, Bob Edgar, Democrat, Pennsylvania (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Media, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
- Plan to Rebuild Steel (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Labor Day Parade, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Financial Sheets, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 10-12)
- Articles regarding Tri-State (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Economic Articles (Box 12, Folder 15)
- American Labor Publications (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Black Struggle (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Catalogs (Box 12, Folder 18)
- "Central American Mobilization" Anti-War Activities and Information, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Chemicals, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Coal Companies and General Information, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- "Coalition for Human Needs", 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Community Ownership (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Customers, Suppliers and Transportation Linkages (Box 12, Folder 24)
- The Deindustrialization of America by Barry Bluestone, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Tri-State Conference Activities, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Finance, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- United States General Accounting Office, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Government Relations, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Gulf Oil, Clippings, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Hi-Tech, Robotization and Computers, Clippings, 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Imports, Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Industrial Areas Foundation (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Industrial Development Agencies (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Job Retraining Information and Organizations (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Labor Notes, International Socialist Publications and Information (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Letters to the Editor, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Mortgage Forclosure, Help and Information (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Pension Funds (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Articles (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Medical Help and Information, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Mellon Bank, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Research on Foreign Aid and Military, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- National and Local Legislation Information regarding Plant Shutdowns, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Pittsburgh, Clippings (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Pittsburgh Power Structure: Corporate Executives and Politicians, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Plant Shutdowns/Economic Dislocation, Effects and Social Consequences, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Pollution, 1982, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Steel Prices, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Rank and File Activities in Steel (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Steeltowns and Politics, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- US Steel South Works: Feasibility Studies, Articles and Information (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Research, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)